Previously on Ghost...
Hell of an engagement ring.
Unfortunately,
that ring belongs to me.
What I need,
only Noma can get me.
If I get you these green cards,
will you please
stall Noma out for me?
Noma said that Lombardi
was her ex.
This is her kid.
This is her Achilles' heel.
What the fuck is this?
You're not being arrested
for drug dealing, Effie.
That's the bitch
that tried to kill me.
This is a RICO.
You're looking at 20 years
federal time.
Weston Holdings
is a fucking Ponzi scheme.
That means my fucking
trust fund money is gone.
Yeah, and the Tejadas'.
You gave our money
to a bunch of motherfuckers.
Now I gotta go
get it the fuck back.
Yeah, I'm into
this honesty thing.
I'm just not into losing.
That's funny,
because you're losing me.
What's that?
A letter from my lawyer.
Saxe says Tariq set me up
to get arrested.
We better not do anything
till we know for sure.
Why would Papi's prints
be at the scene
of Zeke's murder?
It was your mother.
She wanted Lorenzo dead.
I'm so done
with your lying bullshit!
I would have did the same thing
for any of you!
If anybody should be dead,
it's yo' ass.
- I should be dead?
- Yes!
Get the fuck off her!
Don't you ever put your
fucking hands on me again.
Get the fuck out of my house.
How did you even find me?
Your buddy, Monet Tejada.
This battle between us
has gotta end.
Tameika, where's my mom?
Tasha is missing.
- Here.
- Gate.
B, I gotta find my mom, man.
But how the fuck
did Tommy get to her?
Saxe.
Working from beyond
the fucking grave.
He had a fail-safe just in case
anyone figured out
he was a rat.
-Mole.
-What?
Technically,
Saxe was a mole, not a rat.
Who gives a fuck?
It's the same shit.
Either way, that mole knew
where my mom was,
and he told Monet,
and Monet told Tommy.
Fuck.
I mean, why would she do that?
I don't know.
All I know is,
I'm taking Tommy and Monet
- off the fucking map.
- Okay, whoa.
We can't make that move
with Lauren about to testify
and Effie in custody.
If she flips on us,
we're fucked, 'Riq.
-You think--
-Who knows, bro?
I mean, at least your uncle
isn't a threat to us anymore.
You're good with all that,
right?
He's a fucking coward.
Look, I can't even--can't even
think about shit like that
until I know my mom's
all right.
What can I do?
You strapped?
Yeah, I'm strapped,
motherfucker.
Let me see that.
Hurry up.
All right, good looking.
I'ma hit you
when I need you, a'ight?
Bet.
Monet Tejada.
I'm surprised
it's taken this long.
We don't need to chitchat.
That's a lot of product you've
got sitting on them shelves.
You asked for this meeting.
You must have
a solution for me.
For which problem?
Your Wall Street operations
are shut down,
the feds are at the gate,
and weight ain't moving
through the Ivies
because that girl Effie
got locked up.
I did not want to worry you
prematurely.
I was told
it would all be rectified.
Who told you that shit?
That Tariq nigga?
You can't trust him.
Only my streets
is bringing in money right now
because I finessed
the Russians,
took Kai out,
and wiped out the Castillos.
Do I have a solution?
I'm the solution.
Empty promise.
How will you manage
our operations
when your own children want
nothing to do with you?
Look, if you back me,
I'll keep them in line,
get your weight moving again.
Before I could possibly agree
to this,
I need some answers.
What happened to my fiancé,
Mecca?
Tariq! Oh, my God.
-It's been so long.
-Cut the shit.
-Where's Tommy?
-You fucking kidding me.
Is that how you wanna talk
to me?
Okay. Where's Tommy, ma'am?
He's dead.
Didn't you get the memo?
Listen,
this is serious shit.
I need to know where Tommy is.
Now.
All right, I expect
you're not gonna go away
unless you see for yourself.
What are you...
Tariq, he's not here.
He never is.
Come on.
- What did he do?
- Listen.
He went after
my fucking mother, all right?
And I swear to God,
if anything happens to her--
Tariq, I raised your dad,
my son is a drug lord,
his father was a made man,
and I have pictures of you
in diapers,
so just calm down.
Take your hand
off the fucking gun.
Okay, good.
Nobody's gonna hurt you here,
sweetie.
Oh...
What are you drinking?
Hennessy?
I don't usually drink.
Juice box?
Look, I need to find my mother,
and Tommy's
the only fucking person
that knows where she is.
What, are you gonna shoot me
if I don't tell you?
Come on.
That never occurred to you.
Sit down.
You're a good kid,
in spite of
all your role models.
Yeah, Mrs. Egan, I'm afraid
I'm not the same kid
that you remember.
Well, I can see that, baby.
But you know,
I don't know shit.
This woman with red hair--
her name was Monique.
Whoa, whoa, M-Monet?
Her.
So she came to my house,
and she gave me a letter.
She wanted me to give it
to Tommy.
That fucking letter had
my mom's address on it.
Well, I didn't know that,
Tariq.
You know
I try not to get involved.
Listen, if you can tell Tommy
that Monet dropped by,
you can tell him
that I'm looking for him.
Hey, hey, Tariq,
you're still a kid.
And- and what I do know about
my son
is that you never wanna get
on his wrong side.
We both have that in common.
Mecca meant this for me.
Keep it.
I don't want that shit.
You didn't love Mecca?
No.
Your son Zeke.
Mecca was his father.
Yes.
And now you wanna use me
to bring your family back
into your fold.
Interesting choice.
Look, I'm trying
to protect my family.
Wouldn't expect you
to understand that.
Let's be clear.
You don't know anything
about me.
But if I had children,
I'd keep them as far away
from this world as possible,
love.
Well, I tried that shit
with Zeke,
and he's the one
who's dead now.
Yeah, and I'm sorry
for your loss.
Were you trying
to protect Zeke?
Is that what happened
to Mecca?
Look, I ain't admitting
to shit,
but I will tell you this much.
I will kill
to protect my family.
So an ex-lover killed Mecca.
How fucking ordinary.
Well, if that's the case,
you really gonna let a fuckboy
get between our business?
A woman in my position
has to consider all the angles
to stay on top.
Mecca's murder,
I never saw it coming.
He kept you and your son
a secret.
I was so blind,
so in the dark,
it made me feel vulnerable.
And I can't afford that, love.
I understand the need
for that control.
Yeah, well, I'm sure
we have many things in common.
And I can't tolerate deception.
In any form.
I've served you loyally, Noma.
And you'll continue to do so
with a reminder.
Are we clear, Mrs. Tejada?
Crystal.
Good.
Anything suspicious
about the Weston suicide?
Abso-fucking-lutely.
Nothing we can prove.
Circle the wagons.
We need to protect
the witnesses.
Where are we with Morales?
Transferred into federal
custody and processed.
Couple nights in the MCC
will soften her up.
And after Lauren testifies
in front of the grand jury,
we'll have Effie indicted
on attempted murder.
- She'll cave.
- Hmm.
She'll connect Tariq
to the Tejadas,
and then we can charge
Diana Tejada with the RICO,
and she'll fold on the rest
of the organisation.
I'll finish digging
into Morales' records.
These two girls,
Effie and Diana,
both
Stansfield students?
With promising futures.
That's pretty savage.
That's how we play it.
Good afternoon, Miss Baldwin.
We're here to talk you through
the grand jury hearing.
I talked to Cooper Saxe.
How is his death related
to this?
Was that Tariq?
Of course it was.
We're still investigating.
We're not ready
to make that case.
The words "grand jury"
may sound scary,
but it's not a trial.
The process
is merely a formality.
Typically,
an AUSA would take over,
but I've been waived in,
so I'll be with you
every step of the way,
asking the questions.
And no defence,
no cross-examination.
You just say what you know.
They'll assess the evidence
and vote to indict Ms. Morales.
You're not asking me
to blame this on Tariq?
No, no. Effie is our goal here.
This is about getting justice
for you.
Justice?
My life is never gonna be
the same.
I hear you, Lauren.
I do.
But it'll be a life,
and your bravery
will keep others safe.
I wanna see my family.
Soon. I promise.
Please don't do anything crazy
in the home stretch.
You don't wanna expose them,
Lauren.
Yo, what the fuck
you doing here?
It seems y'all can't keep
Noma happy,
so I'm your new boss now.
-You're welcome.
-Fuck, nah.
-No, no.
-Dru, chill the fuck out.
This ain't no game.
So we answer to you now?
If you answer to Noma,
you answer to Monet.
In other words,
no more fucking around.
Cane, Dru,
you back on the streets.
Tell your sister to call me.
And you two
Trading Places motherfuckers
owe me some serious money.
Wipe that fucking smirk
off your face.
Y'all gave my money
to the country club crooks,
so your name
is on that bill now too.
And y'all gotta make
Noma whole again too.
So put your fucking
Beavis and Butt-Heads together
and find a new market.
The only thing keeping you
alive is your debt.
And you.
We need to talk.
Now, why the fuck you telling
my kids I killed Lorenzo?
How the fuck
would I know that shit?
I ain't tell them nothing.
Well, you knew it wasn't GTG
that killed Zeke,
and I'm sure you figured out
the rest of that shit too.
Oh, that's why you sent Tommy
after my mother.
Nigga, I don't know what
the fuck you talking about.
I ain't have shit
to do with that.
But if it was left up to me,
Cane would be digging
your grave right now.
But lucky for you,
you need to keep
your little bitches in line
first.
Effie and Lauren can't talk.
-Am I clear?
-Yes.
Tariq, a moment.
The green cards.
My family received approval.
Yeah, I know that,
but you were supposed
to stall Noma until
we figured something out.
Yet Noma knows everything
and Monet's now
the fucking boss?
This is what I received
from stalling Noma.
Be happy she prevented Monet
from killing you
till the heat was off
of our enterprise.
It will benefit us all
when you are back
in Noma's good graces.
Use the time wisely.
I will.
Hey, what's up? It's Di.
Leave a message.
Diana, get over your shit
and call me back.
We need to talk
about Saxe's letters.
Is Tariq a snitch or not?
Don't do nothing stupid.
And follow me.
You got some fucking balls.
You brought a fucking gun
to my mother's house?
This exact fucking one,
Uncle Tommy.
I swear to my life I'll use it
if you don't tell me
what happened to my mother.
Yeah, all right.
You quit popping off,
and I'll tell you.
Put the gun down first, Tariq.
You wanna know where your
mother is, put the gun away.
We hashed it out, okay?
You got the drop on me.
And then thank God your mother
knocked you the fuck out,
'cause you was about to shoot.
I love you,
but I'll put a bullet in you
to stop you
from killing my mother.
You think you're finally
gonna kill me, huh?
Well, you killed your father.
So pulling the trigger on me
ain't gonna be nothing to you.
No.
I just saved your life, Tommy.
What, you're gonna kill me
while I'm trying to check
on my baby?
Yeah, come here.
You gotta turn him like this.
Towards you,
so he's on his side.
Okay, okay, be careful, please.
I ain't the one
who just knocked his ass out.
He's fine.
He's just sleeping it off.
Why'd you do this?
You had the drop on me.
I've already lost
too much family, Tommy.
We don't need
to kill each other.
Let's dead this shit.
Family.
What about me?
What about Keisha?
You think I wanted
to kill my best friend?
Like that shit was easy?
She was gonna rat on my son
and then she was gonna rat on
you.
-No.
-No, I saved your life again.
Listen to me.
Our blood feud ends now.
Or else we're gonna end up
in the grave
just like Lakeisha,
just like Ghost.
Fuck.
Tasha...
Look, I love you, Tommy.
I never stopped.
Don't ever forget how we've
been there for each other.
We are day-ones.
We're the only ones left.
I know.
I just feel like
I keep losing my people.
So let's not lose each other.
God, Tash, I wish we could
just smoke a blunt
and ride around the city.
I got so much I wanna tell you.
-You know, I got a brother?
-What?
That's insane, Tommy.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, it's a half-brother.
But he got a son.
I'm a actual uncle now.
So you know it's real
when I tell you
I want this shit to be over.
I trust you
with that information.
So is my family safe from you?
'Cause your family's safe
from me.
What the fuck you mean, Tommy?
We are family.
I love you, too, Tash.
But I gotta get
the fuck up out of here.
All right.
Where is she?
I don't know.
When the marshals showed up,
we took off.
But I know she wouldn't
want you going after Monet.
You speak for my mother now.
If you put Monet in the ground,
then you're getting
your mother,
your other sister,
and your grandmother killed.
Uncle Tommy, fuck that noise.
Okay?
Monet made a fucking move
already.
I need to retaliate.
You ain't got no ally.
You ain't got no plan for war.
You need to rethink
your beef with her.
You think I can't handle
a fucking war
by myself, Uncle Tommy?
I know you can't ride one out
from the back of a fucking
college classroom.
Your father tried
to ride one out
from between two worlds.
It's what fucked him up.
If you wanna survive,
you either a civilian
or a gangster.
There ain't no in-between.
Stay in your lane.
All in or all out.
If you get distracted...
you dead.
A'ight,
so say I do hear you out.
Say I'm all in.
You care, right?
You proved that
by having my fucking back.
Oh, Tariq...
this ain't my war.
Plus, in New York,
I'm already dead.
Be smart, Tariq.
Less than 24 hours away,
and polls show Rashad Tate
firmly in the lead
over his rival, AVH,
to be the twelfth district's
democratic nominee.
And in New York,
that's a guaranteed ticket
to Congress.
Okay, okay, okay.
Please, not until after
the election.
Don't jinx my ass.
Taking on Weston Holdings
was brave.
Courage is never something
that I lacked.
No, courage was never
your problem.
Ethical conviction
was your issue,
but you showed me
you are who I hoped
you could be.
And I'm very proud of you.
Thank you.
So maybe we can try again.
Only if I can do it
the right way, baby.
"The right way"?
We will,
of course, be with you...
Rashad...
You know your knees are bad.
Harper, I'm gonna ask you
a third time.
Will you marry me?
-Yes.
-Yes!
Yes!
I love you.
Oh!
So Monet's just
our fucking boss now.
She made the one move she had.
It was smart.
Forcing her kids to work
for her under penalty of death
is smart?
She's a fucking sociopath.
Does it matter?
We ain't got
nowhere else to go.
Oh, no, I forgot.
He's a fucking mama's boy.
Always has been,
always will be.
If I was you,
I'd shut the fuck up.
I'm so tired
of your fucking bullshit.
Do you even care
that she killed our father?
Enough! Hey!
Stop, okay?
This beef ain't between us.
It's Monet again.
She's always
the fucking problem.
Y'all know that.
When will y'all realise
we don't live normal lives?
Seriously.
Dru, I need you
to man the fuck up, okay?
You're not gonna be
a NBA housewife.
And Diana,
let's stop pretending
you're some college
sorority chick, all right?
We're drug dealers.
That's the family business.
That's who we are.
Now, I have
a collection to hit.
You know what?
Fuck both of them.
They're never gonna see us
coming.
And by the time they do,
it'll be too fucking late.
Nice of you to join us.
What the fuck
don't you understand
about family emergency?
I'm here now.
My brother is dead, Brayden.
Show some goddamn unity.
I think you guys
should just all
get out of the city
for a while.
You know, avoid all the media,
cops, all that bullshit.
No, Brayden's right.
I can't go out on the street
without being heckled.
Jesus, you're all
thinking about yourselves.
What about a fucking funeral
for Uncle Lucas?
Oh, Becca's right.
What about Uncle Lucas?
No one's even fucking
going to that.
What the fuck?
Mom, Dad, Becca,
you might wanna get
out of here.
Ain't nobody going nowhere.
Your family owes
my family money.
I have no idea
who the hell you people are,
but we are not in a position
to repay anybody's losses.
- Cane...
- Listen, man.
You're not
in a fucking position
- to not be in a position.
- Cane...
let's fucking handle this
later.
Relax, little man.
Look, everybody
calm the fuck down.
If you don't have the money,
these paintings right here
damn sure don't look fake.
Fucking nice-ass house.
Yeah, check this out, Ma.
This one got your name on it.
Monet.
Yeah, right there.
I'll put this shit up
in the dining room.
Hey...
Let me get that watch,
snowflake.
Oh, dude,
it's a family heirloom.
Oh, my God!
- All right.
- All right. Appreciate it.
I'll make sure I let the nigga
at the pawn shop know that.
Hey, all this shit,
it's just a down payment.
We'll be back
for all this shit.
What the fuck, son?
You had every opportunity
to leave that life behind.
You are not one of them.
Yeah, you didn't learn your
fucking lesson the first time?
Me?
Your brother was the biggest
crook in the generation.
You're gonna act like
this is the first time
you suspected anything?
Yeah, okay.
See if the SEC buys
that bullshit.
This fucking family.
- You spoke to your sister?
- Yeah.
Shit that happened to Pops
really fucked them up.
All right?
Dru and Diana might be out.
Nah.
That ain't gonna work for me.
Yeah, well, you gonna
have to work your magic.
When was you gonna tell me
Effie got locked up?
Yeah, Davis told me.
Can I count on you, Cane?
'Cause me and you both know
that Tariq is not gonna be able
to handle this shit.
Listen, don't trip
about Effie, all right?
She didn't snitch out Tariq
like I asked her to.
But she held it down.
She kept it 100.
Are you--
nigga, you are pussy whipped.
Can't you see this bitch
is out for herself?
Man, fuck it.
I-I'll handle it on my own.
Fuck.
On the gate.
Why are you changing my cell?
Do I look like I'm here
to answer your questions?
Looks like we got
another bad bitch.
Lights out at nine.
Good, you're here. Look.
From what you told me,
you need to leave
this Monet shit alone,
all right?
She said she didn't do it.
Obviously,
she's gonna fucking lie.
I'm only alive
'cause I owe money.
If I may suggest,
when your lawyer
and your homicidal white uncle
both tell you not to start
a war, you should listen.
And we have more pressing shit.
The feds have me on camera
passing a note to Diana.
You gotta get her
charges dropped.
Or else I go down with her.
Trust me, I'm working on that.
What the fuck happened
at Weston Holdings?
You know, I think it was
the fucking
Councilman Tate nigga.
- Shit.
- Yeah.
Okay, I- I'd recommend
not murdering a congressman.
But having leverage on Tate
could be useful.
Oh, you know
that snake-ass motherfucker
is always up for a deal.
That's for damn sure.
I'll take care of that.
And you, my friend,
need to focus on Effie.
She has to go, Tariq.
Whoa, whoa.
Ain't that exactly
what the fuck
you're not supposed to say?
She's not on our side.
If she folds,
we all get jumpsuits.
Didn't she snitch on you
before?
Yes, but it's not that simple.
All right, obviously, the feds
will lock us the fuck up.
But Noma will kill us.
Effie has the picture
that I need
to get out from under
Noma's thumb.
You'll never get to use it
if Lauren testifies,
which reminds me,
she has to go too.
What the fuck are you on
right now, Davis?
You sound like Monet, my nigga.
Stay in your lane.
I don't give a fuck anymore.
Those are your bitches.
Since when is killing
a problem for you?
I learned that killing leads
to more fucking problems.
Listen, I understand
you just lost your brother.
I get exactly how you feel.
I lost my twin sister
right in front
of my fucking eyes, Davis.
But now's not the time
to crash out.
You gotta pull
your shit together.
All right, what if she recants?
What's her incentive?
She gotta feel more in danger
if she testifies
than if she doesn't.
Exactly.
I hear her parents came back
to town after Effie's arrest.
That could be a soft spot.
But recanting won't
outright solve it.
They'd still have time
to trump up some other charges
against Effie.
Unless...
Will Effie talk to you?
Yeah, I think so.
You have to convince her
to do something
she won't wanna do.
Hey!
Drop it. Drop it.
Get the fuck off of me!
You're trying
to fucking kill me?
Tougher than I thought.
You have a visitor.
What happened? You okay?
So I can assume it wasn't you
that sent that warning?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
What the fuck
are you here for then?
I got a plan to get you out.
I don't need shit from you.
My lawyer's coming
to sort this out.
I have my own money.
I'm gonna post my own bail.
You know, you can't post bail,
right, Effie?
Nigga, are you crazy?
Are you trying
to get me killed?
Listen, Davis said
if you post bail,
they have months to indict you.
But if you sit, they have
to impanel a whole grand jury
to indict you in five days.
How does less time help me?
Because once they get
the charges dropped,
they'll have less time
to find out anything else.
You'll walk.
Look, we haven't seen
eye to eye,
but we're on the same team,
right?
Because you need something
from me?
That picture
of Noma's daughter, yes.
I need it.
If I get it,
figure out who she is,
I'll get you out,
and I'll get us out
from under Noma.
Well, I found her already.
The fuck you mean
you found her?
I found her already.
And you're not getting
a goddamn thing
until you get me
the fuck out of here.
All right,
so they need a grand jury
to indict Effie in five days.
That's our window to get Lauren
a reversal story against Effie.
Effie gets clear, we walk free.
I don't think we got
enough time for that.
I will cut
that fucking hand off.
When did baby Rambo's
balls drop, huh?
Listen, listen, listen.
Only way we get Lauren
to change her story
is if we work together.
So both of y'all
shut the fuck up
and listen, all right?
What you got?
Remember when Obi dropped
pictures of our families?
We're gonna threaten
Lauren's parents?
But just with pictures.
Look, she needs to understand
that even WITSEC can't protect
her and her family, bro.
Look, I'ma set up
a meeting with us.
You guys talk to her.
You guys show her the pictures.
We promise her safety
in return for her recanting
her story on Effie.
Dru and I will get the photos.
Bet. I'll have Davis
show y'all where to get them.
Just tell me
when you wanna leave.
I swear to God--
Yo, yo, yo,
shut the fuck up, man.
We got shit to do.
You better have a damn good
reason for calling.
Lauren, listen.
You can't testify, all right?
It's not safe.
So someone's gonna kill me?
The same way you killed Saxe
after I told you
he was talking to Jenny?
That wasn't me.
All right?
Saxe was dirty as fuck.
He dug his grave
100 times over.
How do you even trust the feds?
They can't even keep
their own people safe.
They don't even let you see
your family.
Come on, listen.
I'm the only person
that can help you
in your situation, all right?
And how am I supposed
to trust that?
If I wanted to hurt you,
you've given me
the opportunity to do so
a million times already.
Just trust me.
I got a plan.
Meet up with me,
and we'll speak about it.
Please.
Okay, but it needs to be
in public.
I'll meet you tonight
in Fort Greene Park.
All right, I'll be there.
Thank you.
I know.
We have to keep trying.
I--
Sterling?
Let me call you back.
We need you
to quiet the fuck down,
Mrs. Baldwin.
Honestly, don't trip,
all right?
She lives.
Hey, light skin.
Nice to see you again.
You fucking tricked me?
Lauren, you're not
in any danger.
I tried to save you, remember?
Did you?
Look, I don't care.
I will fuck all y'all up
before I go down.
Look, they're just here
to make a deal.
Face to face so you know
that they're telling the truth.
That's it.
I wouldn't be scared
of the undynamic duo,
but what I would
be scared of...
Is me.
My mom and dad? Really?
What? Cane, what the fuck?
We never spoke about this shit.
- Let them go right now.
- Or what, huh?
You'll slightly puncture me
with a fucking steak knife?
Listen, I don't listen
to this nigga, okay?
I listen to myself, all right?
Now, if I give you my word,
it's bond.
Recant,
forget I fucking know you.
Yeah, you go about
your regular life.
School, family,
back to the future
that you've been
preparing for.
I mean, what, you wanna be
in bum fuck Arizona
being a cashier?
That's all WITSEC has for you,
Lauren, literally.
And what about Effie?
Is she in on this deal?
That's who tried to fucking kill
me.
And I'm gonna need
guarantee from that bitch
before I do shit.
But I swear to God,
if something happens
to my family, it is over.
Listen, let her parents go.
Show her she can trust us.
-Come on.
-Cane.
All right.
But remember, we always know
where to find them.
Jenny and Blanca were right,
weren't they?
The drugs, murders,
it all comes back to you.
No, listen,
it wasn't supposed--
Don't!
This is the last time
you lie to me.
Fuck.
I mean,
even if this shit does work,
we still gotta worry about
the charges against Diana, no?
You got Davis handling
that shit, right?
Yeah.
Right now, in fact.
I just received
the call from AVH.
She's officially conceded
the race.
I'm happy tonight
that virtue and integrity won.
And I couldn't have done it
without my extraordinary staff:
Brushaundria, Jim, Sabrina,
I couldn't have done it
without all of your support.
But mostly,
I couldn't have done it
without the guidance
from my lovely fiancée, Harper.
Come on. Come on up.
-I love you.
-I love you too.
And remember,
New York still leads the way.
New York leads the way.
New York leads the way!
I'm proud of you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
I appreciate you.
What's happening, nigga?
Or shall I say congratulations,
Congressman?
Ah, Davis, I didn't realise
that you were a supporter.
I'm not.
But I have a message for you.
Shall we?
Thank you for
going out to those polls and...
Tariq and the Tejadas know
it was you
who burned them
at Weston Holdings.
You've got a bullet
coming your way.
Are you sure you wanna
threaten me, my nigga?
'Cause after tonight,
I can have your ass
chasing after fucking
ambulances in Trenton.
Now who's threatening who?
There's something you can do
that might earn you some grace.
Get that charges
against Diana Tejada dropped,
and make sure
they back off me as well.
Look at your ass.
Mm-mm.
But you know,
I'm always open
to helping friends in need,
particularly when they donate
large sums of money
to my campaign.
Of course.
Consider it done.
And drink!
Professor Bennet,
I was just looking for you.
Amina Hosseini of The Tribune.
Now's not a good time.
I would love to run a piece
on your love story
with Rashad Tate.
Old flames reuniting
during the campaign.
Well, it would be about
the end of a love story,
a real fucking tragedy.
And nobody wants to read that.
So if you'll excuse me.
Brayden?
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Just getting my shit
out of here.
It's my last day
at Weston Holdings, so...
SEC just cleared me.
You know, they also wanted
to talk to RSJ,
but conveniently,
he's out of the country.
Guess that's one of the perks
of having your own private jet.
Yeah, well,
I'm gonna be stuck on coach
on the way back home
to Columbus, so...
You don't have to go.
Lucas took the blame
for everything
in his suicide note.
Yeah, but that doesn't change
the fact
that I know I was a part of it.
I gotta take a step back.
You know, look at my life.
Start over.
At least you get to.
Brayden, you know how you said
that you were gonna make
all of this go away?
Your uncle wasn't a quitter.
I mean, I- I told you
where he was hiding.
That suicide note,
it- it didn't sound
anything like him.
What are you asking me?
Maybe...
maybe you need
to get out of here too.
I mean, seriously.
Think about
what you're becoming.
It's a little late for that.
- I'm not an idiot.
- I know.
Okay, so this isn't about
getting justice for me.
This is about you trying
to get Effie to turn on Tariq
and bring down
some big drug ring
while you get justice
for your dead boyfriend
and maybe a promotion.
That's what I thought.
Look, at this point,
I want Tariq gone, too,
but what I'm not gonna do
is get up on that stand
and lie for you.
So if you want Effie
to flip on Tariq,
let me talk to her.
Well, what makes you think
you can get Effie to flip?
Because I can tell her
she has no reason
to stay loyal to him.
What do you mean?
Tariq wants her
to keep her mouth shut
and go away
so he can be with me.
Have you been in contact
with Tariq?
Did he tell you that?
Of course not.
But she doesn't know that.
Lauren, I've crossed
so many ethical lines already,
I- I can't ask you to do that.
Jenny, you have no choice.
Either I talk to Effie
or I'm not gonna testify.
And then what?
Too much of a fair fight
last time?
You two play nice now.
This isn't being recorded.
I learned my lesson
about that shit.
The past few months of my life
have been fucking hell.
Do you understand that?
And whatever it is
that you're into,
I'm not a part of it.
Apparently,
Tariq didn't want me dead,
and neither did Brayden.
But the cops showed me pictures
of you two.
So what was that?
You were just trying
to get rid of me?
You're thinking
way too deep into this.
So then what do I need to know?
Because if I'm not 100% sure
that this shit is over,
I have no problem
taking you guys down with me.
Lauren...
I don't give a fuck about you.
Not one.
You say the last couple months
of your life have been hard.
Try since fucking birth.
You've had every single
golden opportunity in the world
and I was never jealous
of that.
But you decided to step out
of your wide-ass,
privileged-ass lane,
and you threatened my future.
You see, this was never
personal, Lauren.
This was just business.
But if you go up there
and you snitch me out,
I'm afraid this is gonna
get personal really quickly.
Are you threatening me?
No, I'm telling you the truth.
Well, I think
you're very confused
on who has the power
in this situation.
- Mm.
- You know what?
I'm not the same Lauren
I used to be.
I didn't see you coming
last time,
but this time,
my eyes are wide open, bitch.
Look, if you recant,
we all walk.
You get your old life back.
We all get our old lives back.
-That's what you want.
-Jesus, you're evil.
All of you are fucking evil.
And somehow, you think
you don't deserve
what you're getting.
Members of the grand jury,
you're here to decide
whether or not
there is sufficient evidence
to indict Josefina Morales
for the felony
of attempted murder.
And to help you make
that decision,
you'll now hear
from the victim in the case,
Lauren Baldwin,
a dean's list student
at Stansfield University.
Miss Baldwin,
would you tell the grand jury
what happened to you?
I know you've
been through a lot.
In a signed victim statement,
you stated that
Miss Morales kidnapped you,
knocked you unconscious,
strapped you to your seat,
and pushed you
into an icy river.
Yes.
That is what you told me
to say.
Lauren,
you signed this statement
under penalty of perjury.
Because you forced me to.
I wasn't well.
I was having panic attacks
over school
and, um, you know,
just the pressure.
I don't--I don't know.
And I took a drive,
and I...
I'm sorry.
I started thinking
about my brother,
who also has panic attacks
and anxiety,
and I must have just
blacked out in my car.
When I woke up,
Jenny Sullivan was in the room
with a doctor that told me
that I was dead.
And she told me if I ever wanna
see my parents again,
I have to say it was Effie
who did this to me.
It is obvious that this witness
has been compromised.
Lauren, are you aware
that you are perjuring yourself
right now?
I was so confused,
as you can imagine.
But she made me believe
that this statement was true.
But it's not.
Sorry, Jenny.
I'm done with your agenda.
I'd like to go home.
What happened?
I don't know how they
got to her, but they did.
We still have Effie in custody.
And you only have a day left
to charge her
before you have to let her go.
And we got nothing
from busting the coffee shop.
They played you.
I'm pulling the plug
before we're embarrassed
any further.
No.
Medina, after all this time,
you know the St. Patricks.
There is a way to save this.
Yeah, pack it up.
Piss on the fire.
This is done.
Are you okay, honey?
Yeah, just really ready to go.
Let's go, baby.
Thank you.
I don't know how you do
this shit all the time,
but you just do.
You just gotta have
a little faith.
Yeah, I didn't have
any other options.
Anyway, as agreed,
turns out Noma's daughter
isn't even a kid anymore.
She's our age,
and she's attending NYU.
Are you fucking kidding me?
This is the name, address,
social media so you can track.
I don't even think
that she knows
that her mom is a criminal.
It's like Noma kept their lives
completely separate.
So um, what happens to me and
this business after you do this?
I mean, you've been on your own
before, right?
I'm sure you can build back up.
Just like that?
After you set me up
at the warehouse.
We're not even now?
All the shit that you said
in Italy,
was that--
that was just nothing?
What about our future?
Effie, tell me why you think
I can trust you.
You went behind my back to Cane
when you should've came to me.
But I'm not tripping.
It's all good.
Let me take you to your dorm.
Come on.
Yo, what are you doing?
Finding my own way,
like I always do.
A'ight, look. Noma's daughter.
That's the key to our freedom.
She'll stop the fucking threats
to our families,
and we won't have to work
for Monet.
Listen, 'Riq,
I don't know if I can.
If you can what?
Ride with you on this.
Look, for me, I just--
I think it's just time to quit.
Cold turkey.
Look, if you can use that
to get me out, cool.
- Wait, wait, you--
- But if it's my head
that Noma or the Tejadas
come for, then--
You waited for this shit to get
this fucking hard to quit, B?
And then you leave me with
the bag to hold for myself.
I killed my fucking uncle,
okay?
He didn't jump. I pushed him.
You did what needed to be done,
Brayden.
Yeah, and it's all
I can fucking think about.
My family will never
be the same.
We ruin people's lives, 'Riq.
I'm just...
I'm not made for it.
-I'm sorry, but--
-Come the fuck on, bro.
Come the fuck on.
I'm sorry. I'm out.
Good luck.
Fuck!
Yo, what's up?
I need to talk to you, 'Riq.
It's about my mom and my dad.
Yeah, she told me.
She thinks I'm how you
found out she killed him,
but I had no idea.
Shit's so fucked up.
I know.
But look, 'Riq,
I gotta get out,
but she'll never let me leave.
She's fucking crazy,
and honestly, I'm scared.
Yeah, I feel you.
I mean, can you believe
she sent Tommy after my mother?
Is she okay?
She's fine.
Tommy said they hashed it out.
If she went after your mom
like that,
how is Monet still alive?
That don't make sense.
Look, because my mom
is still alive, all right?
And that's a win for me.
I don't need no fucking war
between me and your family, D.
That's just gonna end up
with my family
having to go
on the fucking run again.
Fucking Monet.
Fuck.
Okay, look.
What if it didn't start a war?
How is that gonna happen?
Dru hates her,
and I want her ass dead
for what she did to my father.
It's time for Monet to go.
I mean, do you really think
you can ever be free
while she's still alive?
She sent someone
to kill your mother.
You think she won't do that
again?
D, what are you asking me
right now?
I'm asking you to help me.
What about Cane?
Cane will never know.
But we gotta move fast.
We only get one shot.
All right, I'm in.
What do we do?
She's been trying to get me
to come over and talk.
I'll pick her up
from the house
and tell her Dru's waiting
at the penthouse
to hash things out.
I'll pull up right
to where you'll be hiding.
Put two through the window
and drive off.
I'll tell Dru and Cane
I never saw the killer's face.
So you ain't got nothing to say
until we meet up with Dru?
This is some bullshit.
You out here causing drama
when it's finally
your turn to step up
for this family.
Family?
This ain't a fucking family,
Monet.
This is a business.
You killed our father.
What kind of mother does that
to her children?
You're right, D. You're right.
Wait, wait, wait. Listen.
When I had to give Zeke up,
it took something out of me.
I couldn't be soft on you kids.
Dealing was Lorenzo's hustle.
We raised y'all like soldiers,
and it was easier
to see you that way.
Easier to protect you
from the fucked up way
these streets treat you.
Now, I know that's not right,
D, but that's who we were.
Now, you put all this on me,
but what about Lorenzo's hand
in raising you?
He chose this life for us,
not me.
I'm tough on y'all.
Especially you,
because I love you.
And I'm sorry.
I don't know any other way
to show it.
You still ain't got nothing
to say?
Ma, I left something
in the house.
Let- let's go back inside--
Ahh!
Ma.
Ma. Diana.
Oh, fuck.
She's still in surgery.
She's in critical condition.
I wish I had better news,
but uh, it's touch and go.
She sacrificed herself
to save me.
Did you see who did this?
It was Tariq.
Tariq?
He thinks Monet sent Tommy
after his mom.
He's looking for payback.
I'm gonna kill him.
Cane, we don't even know
if Ma is gonna be okay.
Cane, you can't--
we have to stick together.
You hear me?
I'ma kill him.
Tariq gotta go.
Ma, you took our father
from us!
You killed him!
Get the fuck off her.
Don't you ever put your
fucking hands on me again.
Cane!
Yo, yo, wait, wait.
Hold up. Hold up.
She killed our father.
She can't get away with that.
She put Gordo up to it
and had me kill him.
It's either her or us.
We gotta cover our tracks
if we gonna do this.
Then we do exactly
what Monet did to Papi.
We can't do it ourselves.
We use Tariq.
There's no way
Tariq gets out of this alive.
You know Cane will want blood.
-So be it.
-What? No.
-That doesn't sound--
-Diana, we are fighting
for our fucking lives.
Tariq kills Monet.
Cane kills Tariq.
What the fuck, Diana?
You were supposed to hit
'Riq's car
so Cane could take him out
right there.
I don't know
if Tariq is the shooter.
Someone else fucked up
the plan, Dru.
I don't know who.
Tariq ain't stupid, Dru.
Just gotta motivate him.
I still have that letter
that Saxe sent Monet.
We can use that.
You can't serve me.
You didn't even ask
my fucking name.
Scram.
Tell Tommy this is a gift
from Monet Tejada.
- We stick to our story.
- I don't know.
-I don't--
-We stick to our fucking story.
It was Tariq.
Ma, I'm so glad you called.
Tommy told you
not to go after her, Tariq.
What were you doing there?
Listen, Ma.
Diana was in on it, okay?
There wasn't gonna be
any retaliation.
Monet was my mark. Not yours.
I'm your mother. I protect you.
Oh, that's why
you knocked me out.
Hell, yeah,
and I'd do it again.
Listen.
Even if Monet survives,
your hands are clean.
I mean, I'm going back
to Yas and Big Mama.
You are going back to school.
You get your trust,
and then you get out, baby.
Then we can all be together
again.
Ma, I fucked up.
What you mean?
My- my trust fund is gone,
all right?
I lost it in a Ponzi scheme.
What the--boy!
W- was it that Weston shit?
Damn, 'Riq.
What now?
I don't know.
I mean, I thought
I was only escaping Noma.
Wait, who the fuck is Noma?
All right, Noma
is Mecca's boss, all right?
She found out
Mecca was killed.
She came here
looking for Mecca's killers,
and now we've been trying
to fill in his role ever since.
Or you pay with your life.
Tariq, what have you
gotten yourself into?
I mean, it's nothing
I can't figure out.
Look, I just need money.
You know? That power.
That power that makes you
literally untouchable.
That shit that Noma has.
Your dad tried that,
and it took him down.
Yeah, but you know he didn't
do that shit right, Ma.
No, no, no.
Ghost was a lot of things,
but he wasn't stupid.
All right, but I learned
from his mistakes, all right?
They're lessons for me.
All right. There's a way.
But if you take it,
you cannot stop.
You understand?
With Monet shot,
it's a power vacuum.
I cleared the way.
You just need to use it
to get close to Noma
and try to--
Learn everything she knows
so I can end up taking
everything she has
and bringing you home.
But it's a dangerous play,
baby.
You gotta be careful.
Yeah, I know,
but I'm not gonna get you back
and have a life worth living
without taking a risk.
You know?
'Riq, come on.
Just be careful, please.
I got this, Ma.
I hope so.
Junior.
Mom?
What are you--
what are you doing here?
You haven't been home.
Sorry.
Uh, our witness recanted,
and the case blew up.
I'm sorry.
But you're still young,
and it'll only make you
stronger.
You've heard me say it before,
but I am so proud that you
followed in Angela's footsteps.
Yeah, I know.
And Angela
would be proud too.
Um, this uh, came for you
in the mail.
It's from that lawyer,
Cooper Saxe.
And then there was one.
Arms up.
It's in my waist.
Mm.
I see we are all being
more cautious these days.
Follow me.
Obi says you have
a proposition.
Yes, I do.
I wanna work alongside you
so I can elevate.
Once you guys expand,
I can run shit right here.
Bold of you to make demands
after a hit on Monet.
I hear whoever it was
didn't finish the job.
Did you have anything
to do with it?
Nah, that wasn't me.
There seem to be differing
opinions on the matter.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Thought you got away with it,
motherfucker?
- With what?
- Diana saw you, Tariq.
You tried to kill our mother.
D, what the fuck
are they talking about?
Tell them what happened.
You almost killed me too.
-Anya Covington.
-Wait, Cane.
Tariq, what did you just say?
Anya Covington.
Yes, your daughter.
I got people with eyes on her.
I promise you
if anything happens to me
or my family ever,
I'll send them people
right after your daughter.
Clever boy.
Never without a plan, are you?
But perhaps you've flown
too close to the sun, love.
Yo, what the fuck,
Effie?
-I'm so sorry, Tariq.
-What the fuck did you do?
I told Noma that you were
threatening her daughter.
We're working together,
and I have a future with her,
so I couldn't let that happen.
This bitch.
Now thanks to Effie,
I've moved my daughter
to safety.
I've been wanting to do this
for a long time.
Get your ass down!
I think I took one
of those fuckers out!
Yo, B, what the fuck?
How did you know?
Obi called me.
He said he owed you.
Something about green cards.
He said they were gonna
fucking clip you.
I thought you was out, man.
Nah, I couldn't leave you
hanging like that.
Are you fucking kidding me?
What do we do now?
Man, I don't know.
I think we just started
a fucking war, though.